clash-media.com 2009-12-31

# Welcome to Clash-Media!

Clash Media Advertising Limited ("we" or “us”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to on it) sets out how we process your personal data and your rights in respect of that data.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the “Act”), the data controller is Clash Media Advertising Limited of Totara Park House, 34 - 36 Grays Inn Road, London WC1X 8HR

### 1\. INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU

We may collect and process the following data about you:

information that you provide by filling in any forms on our site www.clash-media.co.uk (“our site”) or when otherwise contacting us;  
if you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence;  
details of transactions you carry out through our site and of the fulfilment of your orders;  
details of your visits to our site and the resources that you access.

### 2\. IP ADDRESSES AND COOKIES

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

* For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on your hard drive of your computer. Cookies enable us to improve our service to you, estimate our audience size and usage pattern, store information about your preferences, and recognise you when you return to our site.

You can set your browser up to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you do this you may be unable to enjoy full use of the site and you may not be able to take advantage of certain promotions we may run from time to time.

Please note that entities who advertise on our site may also use cookies, but we do not have access to them or control over them.

### 3\. USES WE MAY MAKE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We use information held about you in the following ways:

to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;  
to provide you with information, products, services or offers that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes;  
to notify you about changes to our service.

### 4\. PASSING YOUR INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES

We may sell your data (or otherwise pass it on) to carefully selected third parties who may use it to contact you in relation to offers in which you expressed an interest when registering on our site.

If you do not want us to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please ensure that you do not tick the relevant boxes situated on the form on which we collect your data (the registration form).

Save where you have given your consent, we do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers. However, we may provide them with aggregate, generalised information about our users.

### 5\. OPTING OUT

If you do not wish us to contact you for marketing purposes, please send an e-mail to [_unsubscribe@clash-media.com unsubscribe@clash-media.com_](mailto:unsubscribe@clash-media.com).

If you do not wish us to pass your details to third parties for marketing purposes, please send an e-mail to us at [_3rdpartyunsubscribe@clash-media.com 3rdpartyunsubscribe@clash-media.com_](mailto:3rdpartyunsubscribe@clash-media.co.uk)

### 6\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;  
if Clash Media Advertising Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets;  
if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply any of our terms and conditions.

### 7\. THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to third party websites. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own terms and privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these sites and their terms and policies.

### 8\. WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, stored at and processed at a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storage and processing.

Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site and any transmission is at your own risk.

### 9\. ACCESS TO INFORMATION

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

### 10\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

### 11\. CONTACT

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [_info@clash-media.com info@clash-media.com_](mailto:info@clash-media.com).

© Clash Media Advertising Limited 2006 - 2007
